
const quizHard = [
  { numberQ :"Question 1.",
    question :'Putting money into traditional red New Year envelopes should be avoided as it brings bad luck.',
    answers :["TRUE","FALSE"],
  correct: "FALSE"
  },

  { numberQ :"Question 2.",
    question :"Egypt is the world's largest producer of dates.",
  answers :["TRUE","FALSE"],
  correct: "TRUE"},

  
  { numberQ :"Question 3.",
    question :"The princess of Caraman-Chimay, a member of the Belgian nobility, was born in the United States.",
  answers :["TRUE","FALSE"],
  correct: "TRUE"},

  
  { numberQ :"Question 4.",
    question :"In the manga 'Death Note', Ryuk is the god of death ",
  answers :["TRUE","FALSE"],
  correct: "TRUE"},

  { numberQ :"Question 5.",
    question :'My birthday is 16 feburary',
  answers :["TRUE","FALSE"],
  correct: "TRUE"},

  {numberQ :"Question 6.",
     question :'Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 was the first game in the series not to include a single-player campaign.',
  answers :["TRUE","FALSE"],
  correct: "TRUE"},

  {numberQ :"Question 7.",
     question :'The video game series The Witcher is based on novels by Polish author Andrzej Sapkowski.',
  answers :["TRUE","FALSE"],
  correct: "TRUE"},

  { numberQ :"Question 8.",
    question :'During the Second World War, Canadians defended Hong Kong.',
  answers :["TRUE","FALSE"],
  correct: "TRUE"},

  { numberQ :"Question 9.",
    question :'Mongolia enjoys around 260 days of sunshine per year.',
  answers :["TRUE","FALSE"],
  correct: "TRUE"},

  { numberQ :"Question 10.",
    question :'The Micmacs arrived on the northeastern coast of America at the same time as the first Vikings.',
  answers :["TRUE","FALSE"],
  correct: "FALSE"},

];